(Howard:)Just try to relax.
We'll be there any minute.
(Howard:)Stuart, stop driving
like an old man.
(Howard:)Speed it up a little.
I'm not an old man!
(Stuart:)I just can't see at night.
(Bernadette:)Here comes another one.
(Bernadette:)Hey, Squinty,
the gas pedal's on the right!
(Stuart:)All right, hang on.
(Stuart:)If you see any pedestrians,
just call 'em out.
(Penny:)Howard and Bernadette's kid
might be born on your birthday.
(Penny:)How cool is that?
Yeah, but I thought this
baby was supposed to ruin
their sex life, not mine.
(Raj:)This is not how
(Raj:)I imagined this day going--
I should be with them right now.
Well, it is
their child.
(Raj:)I know that.
(Raj:)But to be fair,
I've spent nine months
(Raj:)helping Bernadette
get ready for this baby.
(Raj:)And Howard spent five minutes
conceiving it.
(Raj:)And I'm being generous.
(Sheldon:)Five minutes?
(Sheldon:)We must be doing it wrong.
It took us hours.